

Personal Summary

Yun Chung

I'm a graduate of Le Wagon (Tokyo), the highest-rated coding bootcamp in the world, and I'm currently working as a junior full stack developer specializing in React and Express. I love my job because I get to develop products and features that create solutions for our users while also being able to learn, be stretched, and grow as a developer.

Contact

Email yun.chung@mac.com

Mobile 070-3166-5476

Personal Portfolio yunchung.dev

LinkedIn yunchungdev

GitHub yunshine

Skills & Proficiencies

- JavaScript
- React
- TypeScript
- Next.js
- Node.is
- Express
- MongoDB
- Ruby
- Ruby on Rails
- PostgreSQL
- HTML
- CSS, Sass
- jQuery
- Material-UI
- Bootstrap
- Git, GitHub
- Heroku, Netlify

Web Development Projects

DishDev | October 2020 - Present | dishdev.netlify.app

• This MERN stack recipe organization app was primarily built to showcase my ability to develop with React and server-side APIs.

Collocafe | September - October 2020 | collocafe.herokuapp.com

• Built with **JavaScript**, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and a map API, this CRUD app allows users to share and discuss their favorite Tokyo cafes with one another.

Rails Cocktail Recipes | June 2020 | rails-cocktail-recipes.herokuapp.com

• This simple, mobile-friendly **Ruby on Rails** web application is used to create, edit, store, and display cocktail recipes.

OneBite | May 2020 - June 2020 | onebite.fun

• OneBite is a **Ruby on Rails** app that allows users to better utilize online learning. My primary role was to design and develop this app's front-end.

Education

Le Wagon | Tokyo, Japan

Full Stack Web Development | June, 2020

Talbot School of Theology | La Mirada, CA, USA

Master of Divinity, Pastoral Studies | 2006

University of Washington | Seattle, WA, USA

Bachelor of Arts, English | 2000

Previous Work Experience

Junior Full Stack Developer | April 2021 - Present

PlateRate | New York City, NY USA (remote)

• Using React for the frontend and Express for the backend, I develop features for a CRM as well as a restaurant review web app.

Middle School Teacher | September 2016 - February 2020

Shingu Middle School | Seoul, South Korea

• I prepared English lessons and instruction for Korean middle school students.

Manager and English Teacher | February 2012 - August 2016

Paedea English Academy | Seoul, South Korea

• At this private English Academy in Korea, I managed the teaching team while also giving lessons to students.

Pastor | June 2003 - August 2011

Good Stewards Church, LA Open Door Church | Los Angeles, CA, USA

• While providing leadership and counsel for the congregation, I organized and taught at weekly church services and planned various events and activities.